{
    "1": {
        "question": "In the UK, the abbreviation NHS stands for National what Service?",
        "option-one": "Humanity",
        "option-two": "Health",
        "option-three": "Honour",
        "option-four": "Household",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "Which Disney character famously leaves a glass slipper behind at a royal ball?",
        "option-one": "Pocahontas",
        "option-two": "Sleeping Beauty",
        "option-three": "Cinderella",
        "option-four": "something",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    "3": {
        "question": "What name is given to the revolving belt machinery in an airport that delivers checked luggage from the plane to baggage reclaim?",
        "option-one": "Hangar",
        "option-two": "Terminal",
        "option-three": "Concourse",
        "option-four": "Carousel",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    "4": {
        "question": "Which of these brands was chiefly associated with the manufacture of household locks?",
        "option-one": "Phillips",
        "option-two": "Flymo",
        "option-three": "Chubb",
        "option-four": "Ronseal",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "The hammer and sickle is one of the most recognisable symbols of which political ideology?",
        "option-one": "Republicanism",
        "option-two": "Communism",
        "option-three": "Conservatism",
        "option-four": "Liberalism",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "Which toys have been marketed with the phrase “robots in disguise”?",
        "option-one": "Bratz Dolls",
        "option-two": "Sylvanian Families",
        "option-three": "Hatchimals",
        "option-four": "Transformers",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    "7": {
        "question": "What does the word loquacious mean?",
        "option-one": "Angry",
        "option-two": "Chatty",
        "option-three": "Beautiful",
        "option-four": "Shy",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    "8": {
        "question": "Obstetrics is a branch of medicine particularly concerned with what?",
        "option-one": "Childbirth",
        "option-two": "Broken bones",
        "option-three": "Heart conditions",
        "option-four": "Old age",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "In Doctor Who, what was the signature look of the fourth Doctor, as portrayed by Tom Baker?",
        "option-one": "Bow-tie, braces and tweed jacket",
        "option-two": "Wide-brimmed hat and extra long scarf",
        "option-three": "Pinstripe suit and trainers",
        "option-four": "Cape, velvet jacket and frilly shirt",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "Which of these religious observances lasts for the shortest period of time during the calendar year?",
        "option-one": "Ramadan",
        "option-two": "Diwali",
        "option-three": "Lent",
        "option-four": "Hanukkah",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    "11": {
        "question": "At the closest point, which island group is only 50 miles south-east of the coast of Florida?",
        "option-one": "Bahamas",
        "option-two": "US Virgin Islands",
        "option-three": "Turks and Caicos Islands",
        "option-four": "Bermuda",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    "12": {
        "question": "Construction of which of these famous landmarks was completed first?",
        "option-one": "Empire State Building",
        "option-two": "Royal Albert Hall",
        "option-three": "Eiffel Tower",
        "option-four": "Big Ben Clock Tower",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    "13": {
        "question": "Which of these cetaceans is classified as a “toothed whale”?",
        "option-one": "Gray whale",
        "option-two": "Minke whale",
        "option-three": "Sperm whale",
        "option-four": "Humpback whale",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    "14": {
        "question": "Who is the only British politician to have held all four “Great Offices of State” at some point during their career?",
        "option-one": "David Lloyd George",
        "option-two": "Harold Wilson",
        "option-three": "James Callaghan",
        "option-four": "John Major",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    "15": {
        "question": "In 1718, which pirate died in battle off the coast of what is now North Carolina?",
        "option-one": "Calico Jack",
        "option-two": "Blackbeard",
        "option-three": "Bartholomew Roberts",
        "option-four": "Captain Kidd",
        "answer": "2"
    }
}